Boy meets girl. Girl unimpressed. Boy starts band.
Sing Street is a romance, drama, music film directed by John Carney.
A boy growing up in Dublin during the 1980s escapes his strained family life
by starting a band to impress the mysterious girl he likes.
Conor "Cosmo" Lawlor, played by Ferdia Walsh-Peelo.
Raphina, played by Lucy Boynton.
Brendan Lawlor, played by Jack Reynor.
Darren, played by Ben Carolan.
Eamon, played by Mark McKenna.
Ann Lawlor, played by Kelly Thornton.
Sing Street is a 2016 coming-of-age musical comedy-drama film written and
directed by John Carney from a story by Carney and Simon Carmody.
Starring Lucy Boynton, Maria Doyle Kennedy, Aidan Gillen, Jack Reynor, Kelly Thornton and Ferdia Walsh-Peelo,
the story revolves around a teenage boy who forms a band to impress a girl in 1980s Dublin.
It is an international co-production of Ireland, the
United Kingdom and the United States.
The film had its world premiere at the Sundance
Film Festival on 24 January 2016.
It was released in Ireland on 17 March 2016, in the United States
on 15 April and in the United Kingdom on 20 May.
The film received positive reviews from critics, grossed $13.6 million worldwide on a $4 million budget, and
was nominated for Best Motion Picture – Musical or Comedy at the 74th Golden Globe Awards.
The film explores themes of friendship, london, england,
sibling relationship, dublin, ireland, music video.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.